# **Anas Moner**

### Front-End Web Developer

A software developer who graduated from Al-Shorouk university, I have a wide set of technical and professional skills in webdevelopment, including proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, and React.js. My expertise extends to essential skills such asproblem-solving, object-oriented programming (OOP).

ansmoner2000@gmail.com

Al-obour, Egypt

in linkedin.com/in/anas-moner-606183236

+201010304960

anasmoner.vercel.app/

github.com/Anasmoner2022

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor's Degree in Civil Engineering** Al-Shrouk Academy

07/2018 - 10/2023

Grade: Good

# Digital Egypt Pioneers Initiative(DEPI) YAT Learning Centers

05/2024 - Present

Courses

- MERN Stack Proffessional6 Months-Training
  - Bussiness English
- Soft Skills

### PERSONAL PROJECTS

NoteKeeper (08/2024 - 08/2024) 🗹

- I am created an application to create and update and edit anddelete notes and create dark/light mode and more interstingthings by using ECMA Script and html and css

CRUD App (09/2024 - 09/2024) 🗹

I am created a simple crud application by using node. is and express. is and mongodb and multer and other things to enhancemy backend knowladge.

**CERTIFICATES** 

HTML/CSS (08/2024 - 08/2024) 🗹

Git Basics (09/2024 - 09/2024) 🗗

Advanced JavaScript (09/2024 - 09/2024) 🗹

Asynchronous JavaScript (09/2024 - 09/2024)

Advanced React (09/2024 - 10/2024) 🗗

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### SK E-Commerce

### Freelancer

10/2024 - Present

create cosmatics ecommerce for client who start her business, i am creating it with my team to create elegant website and dashaboard. githubRebo

# E-commarce Admin Dashborad

# **Graduation Project**

10/2024 - 10/2024

we create Mern stack project for create admin dashboard and we target to update it to sell it as a template. FrontEndRebo, BackEndRebo.

### **LANGUAGES**

#### English

Professional Working Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

# **SKILLS**

